Schaefer, Vincent; Papers ua902.010
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus, 1891-1993; 1; 21.0 cubic ft.
  - Reports & Publications by Others-- Non-General Electric, 1901-1953; 1978; 1988; 1993; Undated; 1.9
    - Air Pollution Conference Report, Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 78)
    - "A Comparison of Icing Conditions on Mt. Washington with Those Encountered in Flight" W.E. Howell, Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 79)
    - "Concentration of Ice Crystal Nuclei under Various Weather Conditions" W.E. Hubert and H.J. Wells, Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 80)
    - "The Formation of Snow Crystals: Results of Snow Investigation at Aerological Observatory at Friedrichschafen- 1940-1943" E. Wall, Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 81)
    - "Economic Significance of Snowfall and Snow Retention on Western Watersheds" W.W. McLaughlin, Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 82)
    - "Frazil Ice Trouble at Chicago's New Filtration Plant" W.W. DeBerard, Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 83)
    - "Indian Studies Rain Making as Aid to Food Production", Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 84)
    - "La Pluie Artificielle" J. Roulleau, Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 85)
    - "Meteorological Conditions at Selected Airports in Canada Newfoundland and Labrador", Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 86)
    - "Meteorological Problems in Forecasting Mountain Waves" DeVer Colson, Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 87)
    - "On the Methodology of Evaluating Cloud Seeding Operations" Jeeves, LeCam, Neyman, Scott, Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 88)
    - "Periodic Fluctuations in the Ohio Basin Moisture Balance" W.E. Hubert and H.J. Wells, Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 89)
    - "The Problem of Artificial Control of Rainfall on the Globe" Tor Bergeron, Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 90)
    - "Selection of Meteorological Quantities for the Design of Thermal Ice-Prevention Equipment" A.R. Jones and W. Lewis, Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 91)
    - "The Water Equivalent of Snow on Ground" C.A. Mixer, Undated (Box 33 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 92)
- General Electric- Project Cirrus, 1943-1954; 1981; Undated; 2; 9.5 cubic ft.
  In 1952, General Electric published its own "History of Project Cirrus", compiled by Barrington Havens of G.E.'s public relations department. In his introduction, he writes that "[Project Cirrus] was very complex, with a number of subdivisions associated with the main activity. Some of these subdivisions ran consecutively, some operated in parallel, and others intertwined or branched off in variously divergent directions." This preface is relevant to Schaefer's own collection of materials because the "intertwined" nature of Cirrus itself, as well as its roots in Schaefer and Langmuir's previous work, sometimes made it difficult for the archivist to separate Project Cirrus documents from materials that related to cloud seeding efforts but were not strictly part of the work done under the government contract that defined Project Cirrus.
  The archivist made every attempt to be strict with materials placed into the Project Cirrus series, using dates, acknowledgements to the military, and the Army Signal Corp's own stamp to help identify documents as Project Cirrus when needed. Researchers may find it helpful to consult the cloud seeding materials in Series #1 for items documenting the events that led to the project's founding.
  Project Cirrus bloomed from multiple experiments that converged late in 1946. Vincent Schaefer and Irving Langmuir did extensive work for the United States military during World War II. Among their projects was the issue of precipitation static interfering with U.S. Airforce pilots' ability to fly and land safely. (See Series #1, General Electric) Their efforts to deal with the problem took them to the peak of New Hampshire's Mount Washington, where Schaefer and Langmuir observed behaviors of snow and ice crystals that were relevant to their current work but also gave them ideas for future research regarding supercooled water droplets.
  When their contracts with the U.S. military ran out shortly after World War II, Schaefer and Langmuir continued studying behaviors of snow and ice particles in earnest. Schaefer discovered that he could use a type of special plastic called Formvar to capture and preserve snowflakes, some of which can be found in Series #1. These experiments led Schaefer to investigate further the behavior of particles in cloud formations. On a hot July day in 1946, while working with a cold chamber, Schaefer accidentally discovered that the use of dry ice in a supercooled cloud would form instant ice crystals. Drs. Irving Langmuir and Bernard Vonnegut added their expertise to the process, working with silver iodide as well as dry ice. In no time they worked out the potential effects of their discovery on weather modification, and the seeds of Project Cirrus were firmly planted.
  Ultimately, on November 13, 1946, Schaefer led a successful cloud seeding expedition over Mount Greylock in Massachusetts. His efforts convinced the U.S. military to sign a contract with General Electric yet again early in 1947. This time, it was a mutual agreement between G.E., the Army Signal Corps of Engineers, the Air Force, and the Office of Naval Research. The government hoped that fruitful cloud seeding experimentation would open doors for agricultural success and even improved safety for the people of the United States. The project sponsored well over 150 flights as well as ground operations, with 1948-1950 being the major years for flights conducted. Besides basic cloud seeding work, they also experimented with hurricane seeding and wildfire fighting in the fall of 1947. The project wrapped up in September 1952 when the Airforce pilots began to be called away to Korea, and the G.E. team decided they had gone as far as they could with their work.
  This series is divided into three parts: flight data and research, subject files, and reports and publications. Each one highlights various aspects of G.E.'s efforts to work with the military as they explored cloud seeding options in the late 1940s and early 1950s.
  - Flight Data and Research, 1946-1953; Undated; 2.1
    Arranged Alphabetically
    This subseries contains materials on specific flights, though the availability of data ranges from a single page for some flights to multiple pages with photos for other flights. Each one is labeled by flight number, where it took place, what operation was performed, and on what date. There are also files on research efforts that took place on the ground and in the lab, including charts, diagrams, weather observations, and research notebooks. Photographs include particular flights, most of which feature aerial cloud views, but there are also general photos that were not labeled by Schaefer or his colleagues.
    Researchers will also find documents on two extra Project Cirrus missions, one dealing with Hurricane King and the other with Operation Red. Both pursuits took place in the fall of 1947. The former related to cloud seeding a hurricane in order to expend its energy before it made landfall while Operation Red focused on cloud seeding over wildfires in New England. The Hurricane King effort is not to be confused with the Hurricane King of 1950; the Project Cirrus crew named the 1947 hurricane on their own but did not have a title from official weather bureaus.
    Please note that Schaefer's preliminary materials on cloud seeding, as well as data and photos from his 1946 cloud seeding flights, are located in Series #1 because they took place before the official creation of Project Cirrus in 1947.
    - Adiabatic Diagrams, 1950 April-1950 December (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 1)
    - B-17G Airplane- Axis and Viewing Angles, 1947 September 30 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 2)
    - Characteristics of a Good Crystalizer, Undated (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 3)
    - Chart: Corrections for Photograph Horizon, Undated (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 4)
    - Charts, Graphs, and Formulas, Undated (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 5)
    - Climate Research, 1949-1952 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 6)
    - Cloud Observations and Data- "Constellation Flight", 1950 November 04 (Map-tube 1)
    - Cloud Seeding Notes and Data, 1947-1951 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 7-8)
    - Cloud Seeding Notes and Data, 1949-1952 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 9)
    - Diagrams: Seeding Tracks and Stratiform Clouds, Undated (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 10)
    - Discharge Correlations of Gaging Stations, Undated (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 11)
    - Experimental Meteorology Data, 1946-1949 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 12)
    - Flight Notes, 1948 February 19; 1948 February 20 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 13)
    - Flight Summary-Kiah Maynard to Schaefer, Undated (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 14)
    - Flights I-58 Summary Chart, 1947 March 06-1948 December 12 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 15)
    - Flights I-175 Summaries, 1947 September 11-1950 July 13 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 16)
    - Flight #1 Photos, Schenectady, DI Seeding, 1947 September 11; Undated (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 17)
    - Flight #9 Photos, Schenectady, No Identified Operation, 1948 January 22 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 18)
    - Flight #21 Data, Schenectady, DI Pattern Seeding, 1948 April 28 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 19)
    - Flight #21 Photos, Schenectady, DI Pattern Seeding, 1948 April 28 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 20)
    - Flight #23 Data, Cape Cod, DI Seeding- MIT Project, 1948 April 29 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 21)
    - Flight #23 Data, Including Path of B-17, 1948 April 29 (Map-tube 2)
    - Flight #23 Photos and Negatives, 1948 April 29 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 22-24)
    - Flight #24 Schenectady, Seeding, Photos, 1948 April 30 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 25-26)
    - Flight #27 Photo, Schenectady, DI Pattern Seeding, 1948 May 18 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 27)
    - Flight #27 Photos, 1948 May 18 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 28-29)
    - Flight #29 Data, New Jersey Coast, DI Cumulus Seeding, 1948 June 03 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 31)
    - Flight #29 Photos, 1948 June 03 (Box 1 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 32-37)
    - Flight #29 Photos, 1948 June 03 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 1-4)
    - Flight #33 Data, Lake George, DI Seeding, 1948 July 26 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 5)
    - Flight #33 Photos, 1948 July 26 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 6)
    - Flight #36 Photos, Schenectady Water Seeding, 1948 August 04 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 7)
    - Flight #39 Photos, Schenectady, DI Seeding, 1948 August 10 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 8)
    - Flight #45 Data, Albuquerque, SI and Di Seeding, 1948 October 14 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 9-12)
    - Flight #45 Data Charts, 1948 October 14 (Map-tube 2)
    - Flight #45 Photos, 1948 October 14 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 13-14)
    - Flight #45 Photos, Undated (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 15)
    - Flight #48 Data, Schenectady, DI Seeding Pattern, 1948 November 15 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 16)
    - Flight #50 Data, East of Albany, DI Seeding Pattern, 1948 November 17 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 17)
    - Flight #51 Data, Schenectady, DI Pattern Seeding, 1948 November 23 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 18)
    - Flight #52 Data, Schenectady and Amsterdam, DI Pattern Seeding, 1948 November 24 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 19)
    - Flight #53 Data, Schenectady and Rome, DI Pattern Seeding, 1948 November 24 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 20)
    - Flight #53 Photos, 1948 November 24 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 21)
    - Flight #53 Photos, 1948 November 24 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 22)
    - Flight #54 Data Schenectady, DI Pattern Seeding, 1948 December 01 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 23)
    - Flight #57 Data and Photos, East of Albany, SI and DI Seeding Pattern, 1948 December 21 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 24)
    - Flight #58 Data, Albany Area, DI Seeding Pattern, 1948 December 22 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 25)
    - Flight #59 Data, West of Coxsackie, DI Seeding Pattern, 1949 January 14 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 26)
    - Flight #60 Data and Photos, Puerto Rico, Survey, 1949 February 04 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 27)
    - Flight #60 Photo Slides, 1949 February 04 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 28)
    - Flight #61 Data, Puerto Rico, and Water Seeding, 1949 February 05 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 29)
    - Flight #62 Data, Puerto Rico, Water Seeding, 1949 February 05 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 30)
    - Flight #62 and #63 Photos, 1949 February 05; 1949 February 06 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 31)
    - Flight #64 Data, Puerto Rico, Data Seeding, 1949 February 08 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 32)
    - Flight #64 Photo, 1949 February 08 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 33)
    - Flight #65 Data, Puerto Rico, Survey, 1949 February 08 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 34)
    - Flight #65 Photo, 1949 February 08 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 35)
    - Flight #64 or #65 Photos, 1949 February 08 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 36)
    - Flight #66 Data, Puerto Rico, Survey, 1949 February 10 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 37)
    - Flight #67 and #68 Data, Puerto Rico, 1949 February 11 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 38)
    - Flight #67 Photos, 1949 February 11 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 39)
    - Flights #67-70 Photo Slides, 1949 February 11-1949 February 12 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 40)
    - Flights #67 and #68 Charts- Puerto Rico, 1949 February 11 (Flat-file 1A)
    - Flights #69 and #70 Data, Puerto Rico, Survey, 1949 February 12 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 41)
    - Flight #69 Photos, 1949 February 12 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 42)
    - Flight #70 Data, 1949 February 12 (Map-tube 3)
    - Flight #71 Data, South of Lake Ontario, SI and DI Seeding-Pattern, 1949 March 03 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 43)
    - Flight #72 Data, Sprakers, Temperature Soundings, 1949 March 04 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 44)
    - Flight #73 Data and Photos, Albany, SI Seeding-Pattern, 1949 March 10 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 45)
    - Flight #73 Data, 1949 March 10 (Map-tube 3)
    - Flight #73 Photos, 1949 March 10 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 46)
    - Flight #74 Data, West of Syracuse, DI Seeding, 1949 March 15 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 47)
    - Flight #78 Data, Albany Area, Testing Vortex Thermometer, 1949 March 25 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 48)
    - Flight #79 Data, Schenectady, DI Pattern Seeding, 1949 March 30 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 49)
    - Flight #79 Photos, 1949 March 30 (Box 2 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 50)
    - Flight #80 Data, Albany Area, DI Pattern Seeding, 1949 March 31 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 1)
    - Flight #82 Data, Schenectady, DI Seeding, 1949 April 8 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 2)
    - Flight #83 Data, Schenectady, SI Pattern Seeding, 1949 April 18 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 3)
    - Flight #83 Photos, 1949 April 18 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 4)
    - Flight #85 Data and Photos, Schenectady, Instrument Testing, 1949 April 25 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 5)
    - Flights #88 and #89, Schenectady and Ashokan Reservoir, DI Seeding and Instrument Testing, 1949 May 05 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 6)
    - Flight #89 Photos, 1949 May 05 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 7)
    - Flight #99 Data Ballston Spa, Salt Water Seeding, 1949 June 17 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 8)
    - Flight #99 Photos, 1949 June 17 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 9)
    - Flight #103 Albuquerque, DI Seeding, 1949 July 13 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 10)
    - Flights #103-112, Data Progress Reports, 1949 September (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 11)
    - Flight #104 Data and Photo, Albuquerque, DI and Liquid CO2 and Water Seeding, 1949 July 14 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 12)
    - Flight #105 Data: Vertical Cross-Section Forecast, United Nations Air Forces, 1950 July 15 (Oversized 2, Folder 4)
    - Flight #106 Data, Albuquerque, DI Seeding, 1949 July 16 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 13)
    - Flight #106 Photos, 1949 July 16 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 14-15)
    - Flight #107 Data, Albuquerque DI and SI Seeding, 1949 July 18 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 16)
    - Flight #107 Upper Section True Air Plot, 1949 July 18 (Flat-file 1)
    - Flight #108 Data, Albuquerque, DI Seeding, 1949 July 18 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 17)
    - Flight #108 Photos and Negatives, 1949 July 19 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 18)
    - Flight #109 Data, Albuquerque, SI Ground and DI Air Seeding, 1949 July 20 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 19)
    - Flight #109 Photos, 1949 July 20 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 20)
    - Flight #109 and #110 Photo Slides, 1949 July 20-1949 July 21 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 21)
    - Flight #110 Data, Albuquerque, SI Ground and DI Air Seeding, 1949 July 21 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 22-23)
    - Flight #110 Photos and Slides, 1949 July 21 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 24)
    - Flight #110 Photos, 1949 July 21 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 25)
    - Flight #110 Upper Section True Air Plot, 1949 July 21 (Flat-file 1)
    - Flight #111 Data, Albuquerque, SI Ground and DI Air Seeding, 1949 July 22 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 26)
    - Flight #112 Data, Albuquerque, SI Ground and DI Air Seeding, 1949 July 23 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 27)
    - Flight #113 Photos, Schoharie Valley, Observing Ground Seeding, 1949 August 24 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 28)
    - Flight #121 Photos, East of Schenectady, DI Seeding; Ground Operation #17, 1949 September 28 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 29)
    - Flight #126 Data, Albany, Observation, 1949 October 24 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 30)
    - Flight #126 Photos, 1949 October 24 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 31)
    - Flight #128 Data, Schenectady, Observation -GO- 39, 1949 November 10 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 32)
    - Flight #133 Data, Schenectady/Indianapolis, Instrument Test and Weather Observation, 1949 November 30 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 33)
    - Flight #134 Data Indianapolis/Schenectady, Instrument Test -GO-47-48, 1949 December 01 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 34)
    - Flight #136 Data and Photos, Schenectady, Snow Replicas and Vortex Thermometer -GO-55, 1949 December 15 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 35)
    - Flight #137 Data, Cape Cod, DI Seeding with MIT, 1949 December 16 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 36)
    - Flight #137 Photos, 1949 December 16 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 37)
    - Flight #138 Data, Mount Washington, SI Detection -GO-63, 1950 January 04 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 38)
    - Flight #138 Photos, 1960 January 04 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 39)
    - Flight #139 Data, Schenectady/ Mount Washington, Instrument Check and DI Seeding, 1950 January 20 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 40)
    - Flight #139 Photos, 1950 January 20 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 41)
    - Flight #140 Data and Photos, Schenectady, Snow Replicas; GO-71, 1950 January 30 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 42)
    - Flight #140 Photos, 1950 January 30 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 43)
    - Flight #142 Data, Schenectady, DI Clear-Air Seeding, 1950 February 03 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 44)
    - Flight # 142 Photos, 1950 February 3 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 45)
    - Flight #143 Data, Schenectady, Snow Replicas/Vortex Thermometer, 1950 February 06 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 46)
    - Flight #143 Photos, 1950 February 10 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 47)
    - Flight #144 Data, Schenectady, Photos/ Snow Replicas, 1950 February 10 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 48)
    - Flight #144 Photos, 1950 February 10 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 49)
    - Flight #146 Data, Schenectady, DI Seeding/ Snow Replicas, 1950 February 28 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 50)
    - Flight #148 Data, Schenectady, Attempted Vapor Trails, 1950 March 03 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 51)
    - Flight #150 Data, Schenectady, Snow Replicas, 2 Small Photos, 1950 March 20 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 52)
    - Flight #151 Data, Schenectady/ Dayton, Weather Reconnaissance, 1950 March 21 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 53)
    - Flight #151 Photos, 1950 March 21 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 54)
    - Flight #152 Data, Dayton/Schenectady, Weather Reconnaissance, 1950 March 22 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 55)
    - Flight #153 Data, Schenectady, Snow Replicas, 1950 April 10 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 56)
    - Flight #153 Photos, 1950 April 10 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 57)
    - Flight #154 Data, Schenectady/ Amsterdam, Sow Replicas, 1950 April 12 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 58)
    - Flight #154 Photos, 1950 April 12 (Box 3 (2-General Electric- Project Cirrus), Folder 59)